I. Feinberg, Robert Arbitration Records 5548
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- University Loudspeakers, Inc. and IAM, Lodge 1709 AFL-CIO. 4/19/62 (Box 13, Folder 1605)
  Decision: Discharge; Fights and altercations. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Manhattan Wire Goods Co. and IBT, Local 810. 4/27/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1606)
  Decision: Holidays & holiday pay; Tardiness. Contains notes and correspondence.
- American Car and Foundry Division, ACF Industry, Inc. and USA 9/20/62 [Files A&B], 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1607)
  Decision: Elimination of jobs; Assignment to work outside classification. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Long Beach Coast Fuel and IBT, Local 553. 5/1/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1608)
  Decision: Overtime; Seniority. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. and Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions 2/8/63, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 1609)
  Decision: Back pay award; Inability to work due to Strikes, slowdowns or work stoppages. Contains notes, agreements, correspondence and exhibits. This case is of importance as the parties have historically been at odds on the issue and have taken it to Fe
- Armstrong Cork Co. and Rubber Workers' Federal Labor Union, Local #22619, AFL-CIO. 6/20/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1610)
  Decision: Suspension; Absences. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- New York Chain Mfg. Co., Inc. and United Optical Workers, Local 408, AFL-CIO. 7/13/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1611)
  Decision: Holidays and holiday pay; Layoffs. Contains notes, correspondence and agreements.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (Sorg Printing Co.) and N.Y. Typographical Union #6. 7/13/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1612)
  Decision: Jurisdiction; Contracting out; Consolidation. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Capital Cities Broadcasting Corp. and American Federation of Television and Radio Artist. 7/10/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1613)
  Decision: Contractual Duties; Crew size; Schedules of work. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- S & S Corrugated Paper Machinery Co., Inc. and IAM, Dist. 15, AFL-CIO. 8/22/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1614)
  Decision: Grievance and grievance procedure; Arbitration procedure. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Lehigh Portland Cement Co. and CLGW, Local 15, AFL-CIO. 10/4/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1615)
- The Grand Union Co. and RCIA, Local 1262, AFL-CIO 9/24/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1616)
  Decision: Discharge; Applications for employment; Falsification. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Alpha Portland Cement Co. and CLGW, Local 187 AFL-CIO 10/30/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1617)
  Decision: Retirement; Pension plans. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Interstate Yarn Mills, Inc. and IBT, Local 295. 10/6/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1619)
  Decision: Bonuses. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- National Broadcasting Co., Inc. and AFTRA 2/15/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1620)
  Decision: Assignment of new jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (Brooklyn Eagle Press) and New York Typographical Union #6. 12/17/62, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1621)
  Decision: Discharge; Insubordination; Fights and altercations. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (Publishers Printing) and N.Y. Typographical Union #6, 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 1622)
  [File A] 12/14/62. Decision: Contract modification. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. [File B] 7/7/64. Decision: Interpretation of work; Rates of pay. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Universal Atlas Cement Division of United States Steel Corp. and CLGW, Local 189, AFL-CIO. 3/14/63, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 1623)
  Decision: Transfers; Supervisors and foremen; Seniority; Bumping. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Carrier Corp. and SMW, Local 527, AFL-CIO. 3/20/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1624)
  Decision: Withdrawal of existing benefits; Rest periods; Waiver. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Allied N.Y. Services, Inc. and IBT, Local 553, 11/20/62, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 1625)
- The Electric Autolite Co. and UAW, Local #964, AFL-CIO. 3/25/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1626)
  Decision: Assignment to work outside of classification. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. and UE, Local 130, AFL-CIO. 5/31/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1627)
  Decision: Layoffs, Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Jay Julien as Producer of "The Fun Couple" and Actors' Equity Assn. 12/27/62, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 1628)
  Decision: Notice; Repayment to employer. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Lehigh Portland Cement Co. and CLGW, Local #15. 2/19/63 (Box 14, Folder 1629)
  Decision: Posting; Classification of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- E.I. DuPont DeNemours & Co. and the Employees Assn. of the Perth Amboy Works. 5/6/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1630)
  Decision: Reinstatement; Handicapped employees; Medical release. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Hercules Powder Co. and ICW, Local #271, AFL-CIO 5/10/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1631)
  Decision: Layoffs; Seniority. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Lehigh Portland Cement Co. and CLGW, Local 15, AFL-CIO. 4/22/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1632)
  Decision: Promotion (to lower pay grade); Bidding. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- The Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co., Inc. and BCW, Local 484, AFL-CIO 3/7/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1633)
  Decision: Shift Scheduling; Discrimination. Contains notes, correspondence and agreements.
- Koppers Co., Inc. and OCAW, Local 8-92, AFL-CIO. 6/17/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1634)
  Decision: Call-in; Premium pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Custom Products, Division of Kanarr Corp. and Mutual Shop workers Independent Assn. 6/12/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1635)
  Decision: Bumping; Seniority; Testing of employees. Contains notes, correspondence and agreements.
- Remington Rand Office Machines Division of Sperry Rand Corp. and IAM, Dist. 58, Local Lodge #826. 5/23/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1636)
  Decision: Time studies; Incentive pay and incentive systems. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Spector Freight System, Inc. and IBT, Local 707 5/15/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1638)
- Lehigh Portland Cement Co. and CLGW, Local #15. 6/24/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1639)
  Decision: Layoffs; Seniority; Vacations. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Texaco, Inc. and OCAW. 9/4/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1640)
  Decision: Departments; Elimination of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- The DeLaval Separator Co. and IAM, Victory Lodge No. 1598. 10/9/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1641)
  Decision: Arbitrability; Lockout; Holidays and holiday pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- American Bosch Arma Corp., American Bosch Div. and Engineering & Architectural Assn. of the American Federation of Technical Engineers) Local 112, AFL-CIO. 9/23/63, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1642)
  Decisions: Holidays and holiday pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. and Screen Actors Guild, Inc. 8/27/63, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 1643)
  Decisions: Back pay award; Definitions (Employment) Contains notes and correspondence.
- Sperry Gyroscope Co., Division of Sperry Rand Corp. and UE, Local 445, AFL-CIO. 10/25/63, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 1645)
  Decision: Promotions; Seniority, Ability. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Hellenic Lines, Ltd. And Office Employees Int'l Union, Local 153, AFL-CIO. 10/29/63, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 1646)
  Decision: Layoff; Notice. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Arma, Division of American Bosch Arma Corp. and Engineers Assn. of Arma, Local 418 (UE), AFL-CIO. 4/29/64 [1647A], 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1647)
  Decision: Bumping. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Carrier Corp. and SMW, Local 527, AFL-CIO. 7/6/64, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1648)
  Decision: Classification of jobs; Evaluation of job factors. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- The Givandan Corp. and OCAW, Local 8-559. AFL-CIO. 11/15/63, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 1649)
  Decision: Demotion; Ability. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (Bindrite Bindery, Inc.) and N.Y. Paper Cutters & Book Binders Union #119. 12/5/63, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 1651)
  Decision: refusal to pay; rates of pay. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (Arrow Press, Inc.) and N.Y. Paper Cutters and Book Binders Union. Local 119. 3/30/64, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1652)
  Decision: Layoff; Contracting out. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (Security-Columbian Banknote Co.) and N.Y. Printing Pressmen's Union #51. 1/16/64, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1654)
  Decision: Layoff; Ability. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Specter Freight System, Inc. and IBT, Local 707. 12/2/63, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 1655)
  Decision: Discharge; Tardiness. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- Arma Division of American Bosch Arma Corp. and Engineers Assn. of Arma, Local 418 (IUE), AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1656)
  [File A] 3/26/64. Decision: Bumping; Ability. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. [File B] 9/10/64. Decision: Bumping; Ability. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- Riegel Paper Corp. and United Papermakers & Paperworkers, Local 712, AFL-CIO. 7/16/64, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1658)
  Decision: Elimination of jobs; Discrimination; New jobs; Past practices; Managements rights. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Personal Products Corp. and United Papermakers & Paperworkers, Local #535, AFL-CIO. 3/2/64., 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1659)
- Lockheed Aircraft Service Co. and IAM, Lodge 1834, AFL-CIO. 3/25/64, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1660)
  Decision: Seniority; Transfers; Supervisors and foremen. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- American Car and Foundry Division, ACF Industries, Inc. and USA, Local #1652, AFL-CIO. 6/4/64, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1661)
  Decision: Incentive pay and incentive systems. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corp. and USA, Local #897, AFL-CIO. 5/7/64, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1662)
  Decisions: 1) Assignment to work outside classification. 2) Evaluation of job factors. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Air Reduction Sales Co. and Air Reduction Chemical and Carbide Co. and OCAW, Local #8-5760, AFL-CIO. 6/10/64, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 1663)
  Decisions 1) Arbitrability; Timeliness. 2) Transfers; Supervisors and foremen; Seniority. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Ford Instrument Company, Division of Sperry Rand Corp. and IUE, Local 471, AFL-CIO. 12/16/64 [Files A-E], 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1664)
  Decision: Recall; Seniority; Ability. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Anaconda American Brass Co. and UAW, Local 1078, AFL-CIO. 8/18/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1665)
  Decision: Layoffs; Seniority. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. This case is of interest as it examines temporary department-wide layoffs and the departmental/plant seniority issue.
- Anaconda American Brass Co. and Int'l Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local #593, AFL-CIO 8/24/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1666)
  Decision: Bidding; Ability; Training & trial periods. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Whitney Chain Division, Hewitt-Robins, Inc. and UAW, Local Union #1199, AFL-CIO 8/12/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1667)
  Decision: Waiver; Seniority. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. The signing of compensation waivers as a prerequisite to reemployment after a disabling injury is discussed in this case.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (Sorg Printing Co.) and N.Y. Typographical Union #6, 7/10/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1668)
  Decision: Discharge; Improper personal conduct; Plant rules; Working conditions. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. and N.Y. Typographical Union #6 (Box 16, Folder 1669)
  Decision: Contract interpretation; sick leave and sick pay; termination of employment. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (C.P. Young & Co.) and N.Y. Typographical Union #6 8/31/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1670)
  Decision: Discharge; Insubordination. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. and N.Y. Typographical Union #6. 9/4/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1671)
  Decision: holidays and holiday pay; contract interpretation; absences. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. and OCAW, Local #8-2340, AFL-CIO. 9/2/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1672)
  Decision: Suspension; Negligence and carelessness. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Repeat-O-Type Stencil Mfg. Co., Inc. and IBT, Local 210 6/5/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1673)
  Decision: Discharge; Improper work practices; Work rules. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. (Sharon, Pa.) and IUE, Local #617, AFL-CIO. 1/17/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1674)
  Decision: Overtime; Equalization. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. and N.Y. Typographical Union #6, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1675)
  [File A] (Lexi-Craft Typographers Co., Inc.) 9/29/64. Decision: Layoffs; Seniority; Classification of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits. [File B] (Tabard Press Corp.) 9/29/64. Decision: Rates of pay; Schedules of work. Contains notes,
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. (Baltimore, Md.) and IUE, Local 130, AFL-CIO 8/19/65 [Files A-D] (Box 16, Folder 1676)
  Decision: Bargaining units; Jurisdiction; Classification of jobs; Assignment to work outside of classification. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. This is an important and interesting case because it involves a case ordered Arbitrabl
- Univac Division of Sperry Rand Corp. and IAM, Dist. 157, Local Lodge #1063. 10/5/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1677)
  Decision: Consolidation; Transfers; Seniority; Classification of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Publicker Industries, Inc. and Distillery Workers, Local 263, AFL-CIO. 10/19/64 (Box 16, Folder 1678)
  Decision: Vacations and vacation pay; Layoffs. Contains notes, correspondence and agreements.
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. (Columbus, Ohio) and IUE, Local 746, AFL-CIO 11/5/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1679)
  Decision: Layoff; Transfers; Seniority. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- American Urethane, Inc. Subsidiary of Stauffer Chemical Co. and URW, Local #584, AFL-CIO. 12/23/64, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1681)
  Decision: Discharge; Alcoholism, drinking and intoxication; Improper personal conduct. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- General Electric Company and UE, Local 320 AFL-CIO. 2/17/65 [Files A-C], 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1683)
  Decisions: 1) Arbitrability; Timeliness. 2) Recall. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- A.P. Smith Mfg. Co. and USA, Local 2013. 11/24/64, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 1684)
  Decision: Discharge; Absences. Contains notes, correspondence and agreements.
- Black Clawson Co. and IAM, Dist. 137, Lodge 355. 2/1/65, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1685)
  Decision: 1) Overtime; Assignment to work outside classification. 2) Assignment to work outside classification. 3) Time studies. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Container Corp. of America, Mengel Div., and Mengel Div. Employees Union. 4/23/65, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1686)
  Decision: Discharge; Alcoholism, drinking and intoxication. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- The DeLaval Separator Co. and IAM, Victory Lodge #1598. 4/9/65, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1687)
  Decision: Termination of employment; Seniority; Absences. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- General Aniline & Film Corp. and General Industrial Workers Union, Local 146, Inc. AFL-CIO. 4/26/65, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1690)
  Decision: Contracting out. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Carrier Corp. and SMW, Local 527, AFL-CIO 6/24/65, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1692)
  Decision: Evaluation of job factors. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- American Cable & Radio Corp. and CWA, AFL-CIO. 5/26/65, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1693)
  Decision: Removal of work from the bargaining unit; Supervisors & foremen. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. and N.Y. Typographical Union #6, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1695)
  [File A] (Pandick Press) 5/18/65. Decision: Discharge; Absences. Contains notes, agreements and exhibits. [File B] (Peter F. Mallon, Inc.) 5/19/65. Decision: Premium pay. Contains correspondence and exhibits.
- American Smelting & Refining Co. and UAW, Local 603, AFL-CIO. 6/19/65 (Box 17, Folder 1696)
  Decision: Promotions; Testing of employees. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Proctor & Gamble Mfg. Co. and Proctor & Gamble Independent Union of Port Ivory, N.Y. (Ind't. Oil & Chemical Workers, Inc.) 6/14/65, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1697)
  Decision: Refusal to pay; Trial & training period. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- MPO Videotronics, Inc. and Motion Picture Film Editors, Local 771 4/16/65, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1698)
  Decision: Promotions; Seniority. Contains notes, correspondence and agreements. The decision involves a client-demanded promotion of a particular employee.
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. and OCAW, Local #8-742, AFL-CIO (Box 17, Folder 1699)
  Decision: Promotions; Seniority; Ability. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Manhattan District, IRS, U.S. Treasury Dept. and American Fed. Of Gov't. Employees, Lodge 15 AFL-CIO (Petitioner) and National Assn. of Internal Revenue Employees (Intervenor) 8/23/66 [Files A-E], 1966 (Box 17, Folder 1700)
  Decision: Bargaining Units; Public employees. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits. This is an important case that deals with the issue of bargaining units pursuant to Executive Order 10988 of 1962. The tremendous volume of information here provid
- Pathe Laboratories, Inc. and IATSE, Local 702 7/22/65, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 1701)
  Decision: Transfers; Seniority; Classification of Jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. and IUE, Local 601, AFL-CIO 10/11/65, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 1703)
  Decision: Rates of pay in relation to overtime; Premium pay; Holidays and holiday pay; Vacations and vacation pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Rochester Telephone Corp. and CWA. 1/17/66, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 1706)
  Decision: Arbitration procedure; Timeliness. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Armstrong Cork Co. and IAM, Dist. 98, Garden Spot Lodge 928 7/23/65, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 1707)
  Decision: Supervisors and foremen; Seniority; Departments. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Actors Equity Assn. files, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 1709)
  [File A] Alan J. Lerner and Irving Squires (Producers of "On a Clear Day You Can See Forever") and Actors Equity Assn. 6/17/66. Decision: Refusal to pay; Training and trial period. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. [File B] Produ
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (for Court Square Press) and N.Y. Printing Pressmen's Union #51. 10/13/65, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 1710)
  Decision: Discharge; Tardiness; Equipment and physical facilities; Improper work practices. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Allen-Stevens Corp. and IAM, Dist. Lodge #15. 9/24/65, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 1711)
  Decision: Discharge; Falsification. Contains notes and correspondence
- New Jersey Aluminum Extrusion Co., Inc. and USA, Local #5136, AFL-CIO (Box 18, Folder 1713)
  Decision: Vacation pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co., Inc. and BCW, Local 484, AFL-CIO. 2/14/66, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 1714)
  Decision: Back pay award; Leaves of absence; Management rights. Contains notes and correspondence.
- The Western Union Telegraph Co. and the Commercial Telegraphers Union, AFL-CIO. 5/23/66, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 1715)
  Decision: Transfers; Testing of employees. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- Burhnam Corp. and USA, Local #2555, AFL-CIO (Box 18, Folder 1716)
  Decision: Vacation pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. The case revolves around the issue of the vacation pay of deceased employees, and the eligibility of the estate of the deceased to claim vacation pay accrued by the deceased.
- Jay Kay Metal Specialties Corp., and United Industrial Workers of North America, of SIU-AGLIW, AFL-CIO 6/15/66 [Files A-C], 1966 (Box 18, Folder 1717)
  Decision: Welfare agreements and exhibits. In this case, the arbitrator assists in the construction of the company's welfare plan.
- The Bendix Corp. Red Bank Division and IUE, Local 417, AFL-CIO. 3/24/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1718)
  Decision: Assignment to work outside classification; Classification of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Hercules, Inc. and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 884, AFL-CIO 5/31/66 [Files A&B], 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1719)
- Long Island Water Corp. and UWU, Local 365, AFL-CIO. 4/11/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1720)
  Decision: Suspension; Improper personal conduct. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- American Urethane, Inc. and URW, Local No. 584 AFL-CIO. 9/23/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1721)
  Decision: Discharge, Improper job attitude; Equipment and physical facilities. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- American Bosch Arma Corp., American Bosch Div. and IUE, Local #206, AFL-CIO. 4/29/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1722)
  Decision: Discharge; Negligence and carelessness. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (for Turck & Reinfeld, Inc.) and N.Y. Printing Pressmen's Union #51. 5/13/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1723)
  Decision: Discharge; Improper work practices. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Ronson Corp. of Penn. And IAM, Dist. 128, Local Lodge #1724. 5/11/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1724)